- Yes, an exact same.
- No, but it doesn't matter that it is the same.
It's just as fun for it as well.
- It does not matter.
- No no.
So yes!
- The last hole.
- Nice.
- How long should you stand here?
- Yes, it will be all evening.
Probably great.
Check, check, check out.
There he goes.
Alone, in a headlamp.
In a pouring rain and plays mini golf.
So he is completely ...
He is absolutely incredible.
Alexander!
Your amazing person!
- Servant, Mauri!
- I have no words.
When you come here and you just stand here with your headlamp and have not given up.
- No, but it's fantastic fun this.
That's my lifestyle.
- To stand here in the rain in Sundbyberg with a headlamp and drive mini golf.
- That's life.
- Does it take you now to leave in any way or do you feel ready?
- I here more here.
No I have not.
- I just want to see what happens.
- It is good.
She needs this.
We need this.
I need this.
- It will be so unpleasant.
I already know how I start to lose my mood.
- This is very exciting for us.
But Viggo Do you chew chewing gum?
- No absolutely not.
My flora in my mouth is probably good.
- I get it.
- I get a little ... - you can be.
- But it's good, of course.
-Yes it is.
May I also smell?
- You really want it?
- Yes, I want to smell.
Yes ... you just want to clinch.
- If it was completely harmless, how fast would it be for you to lower it?
- Great.
I get so hungry when you say so.
- Do you know anyone else who has this addiction?
- Yes, my friend Cassandra, which I have included in this.
- Can you be a little angry about Vera because she gave you this addiction?
- No!
I'm so happy that she gave me that.
It's a good scent that I can't describe.
You don't think about anything but just that scent.
- If I put on some song that you like and then we massage each other at the same time ...
Then you become so satisfied.
And then just inhale.
- mm, so nice.
- Vidar, you are Vera's little brother.
How does it feel to have a sister who is addicted to rinse aid?
Good.
In business if you follow along, you also usually smell.
- It's completely senseless.
What a human being.
I get a little worried that I can live up to her ...
She does not know that I will come.
- She doesn't have a rush.
She thinks we're at a meeting.
- I'm not saying this for fun, but I'm a little worried about how she should react.
But it also does not feel like your dream situation that someone is starting to cry in front of you.
- I'm used.
Many people start crying.
- Wherever you go to town.
- Yes, they start crying.
I don't know why, but they cry and cry and cry.
- Allright.
Here we go.
- In here it is.
- Will she see me here now?
- I don't think so, because she sits a little further in.
- Is she unstable?
- No, she is doing the top.
But it will be a lot for her, I think.
But we go in.
- We see.
This will be fun.
Experiment.
- Servant man!